you know so i was always an outspoken kid but i feel like i really connected with hip-hop
because the nature of the craft is speaking you know i mean they're not singing like they're
literally like speaking and they're very emphatic and i get a bad rap from like
weak men and women who will be like amanda's a man she talks like a man she's too masculine but
what they don't understand is that like well one i have a deep voice but two like i speak with
conviction like an emcee even when i'm not rapping and like if you think about but like if you think
about emcees especially women emcees like they had to you know like you couldn't have soft emcees at
that time like no like they was they was so minuscule in terms of numbers in the midst of such a big um
field of men that they had to really be brusque with their delivery like remember ladies
like when you say you love me it doesn't matter it goes into my head as just chit chatter like
roxie and shante everybody talked that way that's literally how i talk to this day
so a lot of times when y'all are like oh amanda's this amanda's that no amanda's just an emcee